Guide to the Peter Palmquist Collection of Women in Photography
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographic Materials, 1971-2003; Series II; (222 boxes)
  - Photographic Materials, (117 boxes)
    - Risling, Marion Joy Rowley, 1 color photographic print (Box 300, Folder 1769)
    - Rittenhouse, Jennie Monroe, Mrs. (1863-1940), 1 photographic print (Box 300, Folder 1770)
      Also known as Mrs. Ellis B. Rittenhouse
    - Riviera, Patrizia (born 1956), 4 color 35mm slides (Box 300, Folder 1771)
    - Robbins, Mary E. (born 1859), 1 photographic print (Box 300, Folder 1772)
      Also known as Mrs. G. S. Robbins
    - Roberts, Ruth Kellet (1885-1967), 47 photographic prints (Box 301, Folder 1773)
    - Robertson, Alice Mary (1854-1931), 2 photographic prints (Box 300, Folder 1774)
    - Robertson, Linda, 4 color 35mm slides (Box 300, Folder 1775)
    - Robinson, Mrs., 4 photographic prints (Box 300, Folder 1776)
    - Robinson, Eliza A., Mrs., 2 photographic prints (Box 300, Folder 1777)
    - Robinson, Flavia (born 1926), 1 color 35mm slide (Box 300, Folder 1778)
    - Robinson, Jane A., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 300, Folder 1779)
    - Robinson, W. A., Mrs., 10 photographic prints (Box 300, Folder 1780)
    - Robison, Hana (born 1865), 1 photographic print (Box 300, Folder 1781)
    - Rogers, F. H., Mrs., 2 photographic prints (Box 300, Folder 1782)
    - Rogerson, Doris, 2 photographic prints (Box 300, Folder 1783)
    - Romais, Miriam, 3 color 35mm slides (Box 300, Folder 1784)
    - Roos, Ina, 2 photographic prints (Box 300, Folder 1785)
    - Rosdahl, Elin, 1 photographic print (Box 300, Folder 1786)
    - Rosdahl, Klara, 1 photographic print (Box 300, Folder 1787)
    - Rose, Judi, 1 color photographic print (Box 302, Folder 1788)
    - Rose, May, Miss, 3 color photographic prints (Box 302, Folder 1789)
    - Rosen, Trix (born 1947), 1 color inkjet print (Box 302, Folder 1790)
    - Rosendahl, Hedvig, 8 photographic prints (Box 302, Folder 1791)
    - Rosener, Ann, 3 photographic prints (Box 302, Folder 1792)
    - Rosenkilde, Ellen, 1 photographic print (Box 302, Folder 1793)
    - Rosenthal, Karin (born 1945), 2 photographic prints and 1 color photographic print (Box 302, Folder 1794)
    - Rosner-Kozuch, Talli, 7 color 35mm slides (Box 302, Folder 1795)
    - Ross, Beulah Eleanor, Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 302, Folder 1796)
    - Ross, L. H., Miss, 1 photographic print (Box 302, Folder 1797)
    - Roth, Joan (born 1942), 2 photographic prints (Box 302, Folder 1798)
    - Rothaizer, Shoshana, 1 color 35mm slide (Box 302, Folder 1799)
    - Rothery, Mary, Mrs., 23 photographic prints (Box 302, Folder 1800)
      Also known as Miss Mary Garrity or Miss S. E. Garrity
    - Rousseau, Ann Marie (born 1946), 2 color 35mm slides (Box 302, Folder 1801)
    - Royce, Cynthia, 4 color 35mm slides (Box 302, Folder 1802)
    - Royce, Roana, Mrs. (born circa 1843), 4 photographic prints (Box 302, Folder 1803)
      Also known as Mrs. H. Royce
    - Rudolph, Julia Ann, Mrs. (circa 1820-1900), 39 photographic prints and 2 halftone screens (Box 303, Folder 1804)
      Also known as Julia Ann Raymond, Mrs. James Ferdinand Rudolph, or Julia Ann Swift
    - Russell, Catharine Saxe, Mrs. (born circa 1853), 8 photographic prints (Box 302, Folder 1805)
      Also known as Mrs. Frank E. Russell or Katie Russell
    - Rutbäck, Hanna, 12 photographic prints (Box 302, Folder 1806)
    - Růžičková, Petra (born 1963), 11 color inkjet prints (Box 302, Folder 1807)
    - Rydberg, Amelie, 6 photographic prints (Box 302, Folder 1808)
    - Rydell, Claire, 1 color 35mm slide (Box 302, Folder 1809)
    - Rydholm, Josefine, 1 photographic print (Box 302, Folder 1810)
    - Ryding, Nellie E., Miss, 2 photographic prints (Box 302, Folder 1811)
    - Saba, Mahvash, 1 black and white 35mm transparency (Box 302, Folder 1812)
    - Sabo, Anna K., Miss, 1 photographic print (Box 302, Folder 1813)
      Also known as A. K. Sabo
    - Sackrider, Delzie (1891-1985), 1 photographic print, 1 piece of ephemera, and 1 serial (Box 302, Folder 1814)
      Also known as Delzie Brown or Mrs. Henry Sackrider
    - Sager, Anne (born 1928), 1 color 35mm slide (Box 302, Folder 1815)
    - Sahlberg, Bernhardine, 1 photographic print (Box 302, Folder 1816)
    - Saint Albans, Mary, 1 photographic print (Box 302, Folder 1817)
    - Samson, Eva, Miss, 1 photographic print (Box 302, Folder 1818)
    - Sandahl, Hildur, 1 photographic print (Box 302, Folder 1819)
    - Sandberg, Amanda, 2 photographic prints (Box 302, Folder 1820)
    - Sandberg, Betty, 2 photographic prints (Box 302, Folder 1821)
    - Sandelin, Anna, 2 photographic prints (Box 302, Folder 1822)
      Also known as Emmy & Anna Sandelin
    - Sangunitto, Sarah, Mrs. (born circa 1857), 2 tintypes (Box 302, Folder 1823)
    - Sankey, R. A., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 302, Folder 1824)
    - Sankova, Galina (born 1904), 1 photographic print (Box 302, Folder 1825)
    - Sapountzi, Aliki (born 1947), 9 color 35mm slides (Box 302, Folder 1826)
    - Sarri, Fanny, 4 color 35mm slides (Box 302, Folder 1827)
      Also known as Fani Sarri
    - Sartor, Margaret (born 1959), 4 color 35mm slides (Box 302, Folder 1828)
    - Sasaki, Kanako, 1 color 35mm slide (Box 302, Folder 1829)
    - Sayen, Gertrude (born 1873), 1 color photographic print (Box 302, Folder 1830)
    - Scarlett, Anna Story, Mrs. (born 1860), 60 photographic prints and 1 unbound album (42 photographic prints) (Box 304, Folder 1831-1837)
      Also known as Mrs. F. O. Scarlett
    - Schaaf, Belva Lockwood Harbour (circa 1884-1962), 1 photographic print (Box 305, Folder 1838)
    - Schaaf, Miv Harbour (1920-1998), 19 photographic prints, 17 35mm negatives, and 2 publications (Box 305, Folder 1839)
    - Schaufuss, Laura, 1 photographic print (Box 305, Folder 1840)
    - Schellhous, Martha F. (born circa 1830), 4 stereographs (Box 305, Folder 1841)
      Also known as Mrs. Loran W. Schellhous
    - Scherbatoh, H., Miss, 1 serial (Box 305, Folder 1842)
    - Scheuering, Rosemary (born 1940), 3 color 35mm slides (Box 305, Folder 1843)
    - Schick, A. D., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 305, Folder 1844)
    - Schiff, Nancy Rica, 1 color 35mm slide (Box 305, Folder 1845)
    - Schmidt, Emma, 1 photographic print (Box 305, Folder 1846)
    - Schoenfeld, Diana Lindsay (born 1949), 13 photographic prints and 2 serials (Box 305, Folder 1847)
    - Schooley, Lydia A. Gochnaur, Mrs., 2 photographic prints and 1 stereograph (Box 305, Folder 1848)
    - Schoonover, J. M., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 305, Folder 1849)
    - Schou, Augusta, 1 photographic print (Box 305, Folder 1850)
    - Schrevelius, Mathilda, 1 photographic print (Box 305, Folder 1851)
    - Schröder, Anna, 5 photographic prints (Box 305, Folder 1852)
    - Schulman, Arlene (born 1961), 1 color 35mm slide (Box 305, Folder 1853)
    - Schultze, Angelika, 1 color 35mm slide (Box 305, Folder 1854)
    - Schulze, Hortense, Mrs., 2 photographic prints (Box 305, Folder 1855)
    - Schuman, Hinda, 3 color 35mm slides (Box 305, Folder 1856)
    - Schütze, Eva Watson, Mrs. (1867-1935), 2 serials (Box 305, Folder 1857)
      Also known as Eva Lawrence Watson or Eva Watson-Schütze
    - Scianghetti, Bärbel M., 1 photographic print and 3 color 35mm slides (Box 305, Folder 1858)
    - Scott, Lola V., 2 photographic prints (Box 305, Folder 1859)
    - Scott, S. B., 2 color photographic prints (Box 305, Folder 1860)
    - Scougale, Melissa, Miss, 1 photographic print (Box 305, Folder 1861)
    - Scranton, Jeanne C. (born 1937), 3 color photographic prints (Box 305, Folder 1862)
    - Scully, Julia (born 1929), 1 serial (Box 305, Folder 1863)
    - Sebanz, Victoria, 2 color 35mm slides (Box 305, Folder 1864)
    - Seely, Dorothy M. (born 1892), 8 photographic prints (Box 305, Folder 1865)
      Also known as Seeley Studio
    - Sefrén, Louise, 2 photographic prints (Box 305, Folder 1866)
    - Seligman, Sharon, 6 color 35mm slides (Box 305, Folder 1867)
    - Selin, Hilma, 2 photographic prints (Box 305, Folder 1868)
    - Seto, Reiko (born 1962), 2 color photographic prints and 2 color 35mm slides (Box 305, Folder 1869)
    - Sevelius, Augusta, 1 photographic print (Box 305, Folder 1870)
    - Shaffer, Becky, 1 color 35mm slide (Box 305, Folder 1871)
    - Shanks, Ann Zane (born 1927), 1 serial (Box 305, Folder 1872)
    - Shannon, Julia, Mrs. (born circa 1812), 12 photographic prints (Box 305, Folder 1873)
    - Sharland, 1 serial (Box 305, Folder 1874)
    - Shaw, Sophronia Caroline, Mrs. (1847-1931), 3 photographic prints (Box 305, Folder 1875)
      Also known as Shaw & Lambert
    - Sheehan, Sue, 1 color inkjet print (Box 306, Folder 1876)
    - Sheridan, Lisa, 1 serial (Box 306, Folder 1877)
    - Sheridan, Louise, 1 photographic print (Box 306, Folder 1878)
    - Shields, Melissa, 5 color photographic prints (Box 306, Folder 1879)
    - Shields, Tracy Jean, 7 color 35mm slides (Box 306, Folder 1880)
    - Shira. O. M., Miss, 3 photographic prints (Box 306, Folder 1881)
    - Shisler, Mary K., 1 photographic print (Box 306, Folder 1882)
    - Shultz, Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 306, Folder 1883)
    - Siemer, Debbie, 17 color photographic prints (Box 306, Folder 1884)
    - Sihvonen, Laura, 8 color photographic prints (Box 306, Folder 1885)
    - Sikström, Elisabeth, 1 photographic print (Box 306, Folder 1886)
    - Silva, Susan (born 1947), 1 photographic print (Box 306, Folder 1887)
    - Silver, Florence Clara (1918-1969), 1 photographic print (Box 306, Folder 1888)
      Also known as Florence Clara Smith
    - Simonite, Patricia, 1 photographic print and 3 color 35mm slides (Box 306, Folder 1889)
      Also known as Trish Simonite
    - Simpson, Rachel Emily, 3 color 35mm slides (Box 306, Folder 1890)
    - Sirius, Jean (born 1949), 1 photographic print and 4 color photographic prints (Box 306, Folder 1891)
    - Sittler, G. W., Mrs., 3 photographic prints (Box 306, Folder 1892)
    - Sjögren, Hildur, 1 photographic print (Box 306, Folder 1893)
    - Sjöman, Rosalie, 2 photographic prints (Box 306, Folder 1894)
    - Sjostrom, Lydia, 1 photographic print (Box 306, Folder 1895)
    - Skeel, Adelaide, Miss, 1 photographic print (Box 306, Folder 1896)
    - Skolas, Julia, Miss, 2 photographic prints (Box 306, Folder 1897)
    - Smith, Miss, 2 photographic prints (Box 306, Folder 1898)
      Also known as Misses Smith & Loomiller
    - Smith, Adelina C. (born circa 1869), 1 photographic print (Box 306, Folder 1899)
      Also known as Cathedral Studio
    - Smith, Agnes J., 1 photogravure (Box 306, Folder 1900)
    - Smith, Alice Whitney (born circa 1888), 2 photographic prints (Box 306, Folder 1901)
      Also known as McDonough & Smith or Mrs. S. B. Smith
    - Smith, B., Mrs., 3 photographic prints (Box 306, Folder 1902)
    - Smith, Catherine, Miss (born circa 1835), 17 photographic prints (Box 306, Folder 1903)
    - Smith, Catherine A. N., Mrs., 1 photographic print and 4 tintypes (Box 306, Folder 1904)
    - Smith, Clara Sheldon, Mrs. (1862-1939), 12 photographic prints, 3 color photographic prints, and 2 color diffusion transfer prints (Box 306, Folder 1905)
      Also known as Mrs. Frank E. Smith
    - Smith, Dorothy J., Mrs., 1 color photographic print (Box 306, Folder 1906)
    - Smith, Ethel M. (1886-1964), 1 serial (Box 306, Folder 1907)
    - Smith, Flora, 1 photographic print (Box 306, Folder 1908)
    - Smith, Gennie, Mrs. (born circa 1854), 1 photographic print (Box 306, Folder 1909)
      Also known as Mrs. Daniel W. Smith
    - Smith, Jessie (1888-1984), 2 serials (Box 306, Folder 1910)
    - Smith, Margaret M. (circa 1904-1991), 1 color photographic print (Box 307, Folder 1911)
    - Smith, Mary E. (born 1857), 1 photographic print (Box 307, Folder 1912)
    - Smith, May L., 1 serial (Box 307, Folder 1913)
    - Smith, Maybelle, 3 photographic prints (Box 307, Folder 1914)
    - Smith, R. A., Mrs., 7 photographic prints (Box 307, Folder 1915)
    - Smith, Sarah Ernestine Potter, 3 photographic prints (Box 307, Folder 1916)
    - Smithson, Aline (born 1953), 2 color 35mm slides (Box 307, Folder 1917)
    - Smorthwaite, Emma, Mrs. (1840-1922), 2 photographic prints (Box 307, Folder 1918)
    - Snell, Rhoda M., 2 photographic prints (Box 307, Folder 1919)
    - Snow, B. L., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 307, Folder 1920)
    - Söderlund, Gerda, 2 photographic prints (Box 307, Folder 1921)
    - Sokolow, Leslie (born 1964), 9 color 35mm slides (Box 307, Folder 1922)
    - Solberg, Augusta, 3 photographic prints (Box 307, Folder 1923)
    - Sonnesen, Beatrice, Miss, 3 photographic prints (Box 307, Folder 1924)
    - Spain, Darlene, 5 photographic prints, 1 color photographic print, 4 halftone screens, 24 color 35mm slides, and 1 serial (Box 307, Folder 1925)
      Also known as Dar Spain
    - Spaulding, L. H., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 307, Folder 1926)
    - Specht, Jill, 18 color 35mm slides (Box 307, Folder 1927)
    - Spence, Miss, 2 photographic prints (Box 307, Folder 1928)
    - Spencer, Ema, Miss (1857-1941), 4 photographic prints and 1 photogravure (Box 307, Folder 1929)
    - Spencer, Erin (born 1967), 4 color 35mm slides (Box 307, Folder 1930)
    - Spencer, Mabel, Miss (born 1887), 2 photographic prints (Box 307, Folder 1931)
      Also known as Misses Spencer & Stolte
    - Spencer, Mary, Miss, 1 photographic print (Box 307, Folder 1932)
    - Sperry, Myra E., Mrs. (born 1862), 2 photographic prints (Box 307, Folder 1933)
    - Spesert, Mary Jane (1888-1936), 19 photographic prints, 2 stereographs, and 1 fabric cyanotype print (Box 307, Folder 1934)
    - Sprake, Bertha R., Miss (born circa 1854), 1 photographic print (Box 307, Folder 1935)
    - Sprauer, Apollonia, Mrs. (born 1851), 4 photographic prints (Box 307, Folder 1936)
    - Sprinkle, Annie (born 1954), 1 serial (Box 307, Folder 1937)
    - Stacy, Maud (born 1872), 1 photographic print (Box 307, Folder 1938)
    - Stafford, Charles, Mrs., 2 photographic prints (Box 307, Folder 1939)
    - Ståhl, Anna, 2 photographic prints (Box 307, Folder 1940)
    - Stanbery, Katherine Sheward, Miss (1870-1928), 1 serial (Box 307, Folder 1941)
      Also known as Katharine Stanbery Burgess or Mrs. Levi J. Burgess
    - Stanbery, Mary R., Mrs. (1842-1906), 1 serial (Box 307, Folder 1942)
      Also known as Mrs. George A. Stanbery
    - Standish, Barbara Stuart, 3 serials (Box 308, Folder 1943)
      Also known as Mrs. L. Whitney Standish
    - Starkey, Jessica Robin (born 1976), 1 photographic print (Box 308, Folder 1944)
    - Stebbins, Sarah L., Mrs. (born circa 1833), 2 photographic prints (Box 308, Folder 1945)
    - Steen, Mary, 4 photographic prints (Box 308, Folder 1946)
    - Steinhauser, Judith H. (born 1941), 1 serial (Box 308, Folder 1947)
      Also known as Judith Harold-Steinhauser
    - Steinmann, Catherine (born 1947), 37 35mm slides (Box 308, Folder 1948)
    - Stellmann, Edith Kinney (circa 1885-1957), 1 photographic print (Box 308, Folder 1949)
      Also known as Mrs. Louis J. Stellman
    - Stenman, Laura, 1 photographic print (Box 308, Folder 1950)
    - Stenström, Anna, 1 photographic print (Box 308, Folder 1951)
    - Stephanson, E., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 308, Folder 1952)
    - Sterling, Hannah N., Mrs. (born circa 1830), 3 photographic prints (Box 308, Folder 1953)
      Also known as Mrs. Hannah N. Stirling
    - Sterner, Agnes, 1 photographic print (Box 308, Folder 1954)
    - Stevens, Cathy, 1 serial (Box 308, Folder 1955)
    - Stevens, Jane M. (born 1947), 2 photographic prints (Box 308, Folder 1956)
    - Stevenson, Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 308, Folder 1957)
    - Stewart, Peggy (1887-1967), 1 photographic print (Box 308, Folder 1958)
    - Stewart, W. M., Mrs., 1 serial (Box 308, Folder 1959)
    - St-Hilaire, L., 1 photographic print (Box 308, Folder 1960)
    - Stickney, Josiah, Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 308, Folder 1961)
    - Stickney, L., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 308, Folder 1962)
    - Stinson, Maude Evangeline (1872-1963), 1 color photographic print (Box 308, Folder 1963)
    - Stockbridge, Nellie Jane (1868-1965), 8 photographic prints and 8 film negatives (Box 308, Folder 1964)
    - Stockwell, Ula C. (born 1875), 1 photographic print (Box 308, Folder 1965)
    - Stokes, Emily, Mrs., 41 photographic prints (Box 309, Folder 1966-1969)
    - Stone, Nelle W., 1 photographic print (Box 308, Folder 1970)
    - Stone, Susannah, Mrs. (born circa 1831), 3 photographic prints (Box 308, Folder 1971)
      Also known as Mrs. T. P. Stone
    - Stratböcker, A. Juliane Frederikke, 3 photographic prints (Box 308, Folder 1972)
      Also known as Julie Stratböcker
    - Strock, Hattie, Mrs. (born 1865), 3 photographic prints (Box 308, Folder 1973)
      Also known as Mrs. M. L. Strock
    - Stroll, Suzie, 3 color 35mm slides (Box 308, Folder 1974)
    - Stuart, Mrs., 12 photographic prints (Box 308, Folder 1975)
    - Stummer, Helen M. (born 1936), 2 color 35mm slides (Box 308, Folder 1976)
    - Sulik, Mary Ann, 2 color 35mm slides (Box 308, Folder 1977)
    - Sullivan, May Kellogg, 2 photographic prints (Box 308, Folder 1978)
      Also known as May L. Kellogg
    - Sunday, Elisabeth (born 1958), 1 photographic print and 6 color 35mm slides (Box 308, Folder 1979)
    - Sundbeck, Calla, 1 photographic print (Box 308, Folder 1980)
    - Sundberg, Maria, 1 photographic print (Box 308, Folder 1981)
    - Sunderland, Lucy, Mrs., 6 photographic prints (Box 308, Folder 1982)
      Also known as Mrs. J. C. Sunderland
    - Surles, Misses, 1 photographic print (Box 308, Folder 1983)
    - Svanström, Livia, 9 photographic prints (Box 308, Folder 1984)
    - Svendsen, Margrethe, 1 photographic print (Box 308, Folder 1985)
    - Svenson, Lotten, 1 photographic print (Box 308, Folder 1986)
    - Swalin, Alma, 1 photographic print (Box 310, Folder 1987)
    - Swan, Emma, 2 photographic prints (Box 310, Folder 1988)
    - Swensson, Alma, 2 photographic prints (Box 310, Folder 1989)
    - Swift, S. J., Mrs., 2 photographic prints (Box 310, Folder 1990)
    - Swisher, Katie Irene (born 1981), 1 photographic print (Box 310, Folder 1991)
    - Swisher, Mary (born 1937), 2 photographic prints (Box 310, Folder 1992)
    - Swoape, Sue, Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 310, Folder 1993)
    - Sykes, Mabel, 2 photographic prints (Box 310, Folder 1994)
    - Tackitt, Carrie, 4 photographic prints (Box 310, Folder 1995)
    - Talbot, Constance (1811-1880), 2 color photographic prints and 2 color 35mm negatives (Box 310, Folder 1996)
      Also known as Mrs. William Henry Fox Talbot
    - Tannenbaum, Susan Rae, 1 color 35mm slide (Box 310, Folder 1997)
    - Tape, Mary, Mrs. (1857-1934), 2 photographic prints and 5 color 35mm slides (Box 310, Folder 1998)
    - Tash, Dora Clark, 1 piece of ephemera (Box 310, Folder 1999)
    - Tate, M. J., Mrs., 9 photographic prints (Box 310, Folder 2000)
    - Tatu, Dawn Alexandra (born 1970), 1 photographic print (Box 310, Folder 2001)
      Also known as Alexandra Tatu Profant or Sasha Tatu
    - Taylor, Carrie P., Mrs. (born circa 1855), 2 photographic prints (Box 310, Folder 2002)
      Also known as Mrs. Schuyler M. Taylor
    - Teeter, J. P., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 310, Folder 2003)
    - Tegström, Henny, 1 photographic print (Box 310, Folder 2004)
    - Teller, Helene, 1 photographic print (Box 310, Folder 2005)
      Also known as Helena Tellerova
    - Ten Eyck, M. C., Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 310, Folder 2006)
    - Tennant, Mary W., Mrs. (born circa 1863), 1 photographic print (Box 310, Folder 2007)
    - Terry, Lois, Mrs., 1 photographic print (Box 310, Folder 2008)
    - Tesch, Maria (circa 1850-1936), 40 photographic prints (Box 310, Folder 2009)
    - Thayer, Ida (born circa 1863), 1 photographic print (Box 310, Folder 2010)
    - Thayer, M. E., Mrs., 2 photographic prints (Box 310, Folder 2011)
    - Thelin, Agusta, 1 photographic print (Box 310, Folder 2012)
    - Thompson, Ada A., 1 photographic print (Box 310, Folder 2013)
    - Thompson, Dody W. (born 1923), 1 serial (Box 310, Folder 2014)
      Also known as Dody Warren
    - Thompson, Frances S., 89 photographic prints (Box 311-312, Folder 2015-2039)
    - Thompson, Rosalie (1831-1923), 6 photographic prints (Box 310, Folder 2040)
      Also known as Mrs. George C. Thompson, Rosella Thompson, Rosalin Thompson, or Rosalia Thompson
    - Thomsen, Marie, 1 photographic print (Box 310, Folder 2041)
    - Thornley, C. A., Miss, 1 photographic print (Box 310, Folder 2042)
    - Tidwell, Belinda, 1 serial (Box 310, Folder 2043)
    - Tillander, Jenny, 2 photographic prints (Box 310, Folder 2044)
    - Timby, Kim, 3 photographic prints (Box 310, Folder 2045)
    - Tippit, Celia L. (born 1936), 1 color photographic print (Box 310, Folder 2046)
    - Todd, Beverly J., 1 color photographic print (Box 310, Folder 2047)
    - Toll, Brooke, 1 color 35mm slide (Box 310, Folder 2048)
    - Tondro, Cassandra (born 1954), 3 color 35mm slides (Box 310, Folder 2049)
      Also known as Cassie Tondro
    - Tonn, Lina, 6 photographic prints (Box 310, Folder 2050)
    - Towne, Anna F., Miss (born 1857), 1 photographic print and 1 piece of ephemera (Box 310, Folder 2051)
      Also known as Towne & Whitney
    - Townsend, Louisa A., Mrs. (born 1857), 5 photographic prints (Box 310, Folder 2052)
      Also known as Mrs. A. P. Townsend
    - Train, Phebe Goodell (born circa 1850), 1 photographic print (Box 310, Folder 2053)
      Also known as Mrs. Edgar Train
    - Traub, Barbara (born 1960), 1 color photographic print and 1 color inkjet print (Box 313, Folder 2054)
    - Trauth, Beti Webb, 3 color photographic prints and 1 serial (Box 313, Folder 2055)
    - Triller, Marie (born 1956), 8 color 35mm slides and 2 serials (Box 313, Folder 2056)
    - Tripp, Caroline, Mrs. (born circa 1843), 1 photographic print (Box 313, Folder 2057)
      Also known as Mrs. M. K. Tripp
    - Trovall-Lütz, Lilly, 1 photographic print (Box 313, Folder 2058)
    - Tuell, Ella M., 1 album (58 photographic prints) (Box 313)
    - Turbeville, Deborah (born 1938), 1 serial (Box 313, Folder 2059)
    - Turk, Ellen Fisher, 3 color 35mm slides (Box 313, Folder 2060)
    - Turner, E. M., Miss, 1 photographic print (Box 313, Folder 2061)
    - Turner, Sheila A. (born 1961), 4 color 35mm slides (Box 313, Folder 2062)
    - Tuxford, Brenda (born 1938), 2 color photographic prints and 2 etchings (Box 313, Folder 2063)
    - Tweed, Annie M., 1 photographic print (Box 313, Folder 2064)
      Also known as Miss Anna M. Tweed
    - Tweedy-Holmes, Karen (born 1942), 1 serial (Box 313, Folder 2065)
    - Tyler, May E., Mrs. (1851-1892), 7 photographic prints (Box 313, Folder 2066)
      Also known as Mrs. Mae E. Tyler
    - Underell, Geraldine, Mrs., 1 serial (Box 313, Folder 2067)
    - Underhill, Linn B. (born 1936), 2 color 35mm slides (Box 313, Folder 2068)
    - Urminska, Natalia Maria, 1 photographic print, 6 color photographic prints, and 4 color inkjet prints (Box 313, Folder 2069)
      Also known as Natalie Urminska
    - Urminska, Olga (born 1942), 2 color inkjet prints (Box 313, Folder 2070)
    - Urminska, Suzanna Anna, 10 color photographic prints and 1 book (Box 313, Folder 2071)
    - Vág, Anna-Mária (born 1975), 10 color inkjet prints and 1 piece of ephemera (Box 313, Folder 2072)
    - Valentin, Helene, 2 photographic prints (Box 313, Folder 2073)
    - Valentine, Olivia (born 1979), 2 color 35mm slides (Box 313, Folder 2074)
    - Van Housen, M. E., Mrs. (born circa 1840), 4 photographic prints (Box 313, Folder 2075)
      Also known as Mrs. M. A. Van Housen
    - Van Ronk, Marion, Dr. (circa 1911-2001), 118 photographic prints, 1821 color film negatives, 100 color photographic prints, 300 120mm color slides, 8113 35mm color slides, and 334 film negatives (Box 314-327, Folder 2076-2372)